Hello hello everyone how are you all I am
your personal advisor Amit Raj Sharma and
you are watching Yudh Real in today's video
we will understand the details of health care plan of Kotak Mahindra or should we say
Contact General Insurance Company Limited
this plan is available in both categories
individual as well as family floater
policy term in this you get one
year 2 years 3 years means for as many years you can take the plan
you can take it
entries limited from 18 years to 65 years
but if you want to cover someone individually then at
least
5 years is fine there the
age limit for dependent children is from 91 days to maximum 25
years you get this plan in two variants
axel and premium sum insured limit
talk about with axel from 2 lakh
to 4 lakh with premium from 5 lakh
to 25 lakh in all health insurance
policies you get
up to the infection hospitalization support same thing is here
also  There is 30 days free hospitalization
with both the options and 60 days
post hospitalization, which means seven days
post hospitalization. With both the options, there is
150 days treatment which is
listed above under cover. In both the options,
you get up to ₹15,100 as per hospitalization on ambulance expenses.
When you renew the policy, it does
not matter whether you have a claim or
not. You will get free
health check-ups in the policy year which are on your skin.
You get a bonus ranging from 10% to 50%, which you can avail if the policy is claim-free.
If you
take the plan as a family floater, then
with the Excel option, there should be a minimum sum assured of Rs. 3 lakh.
You do not get to see any such limit in the premium. There is a
waiting period of 48 months on pre-existing diseases, health problems already covered. Now, there is a
cataract hernia or knee replacement, for such conditions,
you get a 24-month insurance cover while sleeping.  There is a waiting period.
Lifetime validity is available with both the options. There is a waiting period of
15 days for TDS. You
get a free look period of 30 days. Now you
can increase your cover. There are different types
of advances. What I mentioned here was
your basic plan, after that add-ons
start, like if a patient is admitted in Delhi hospital for
three days, then
he will get these benefits of Delhi.
Depending on the number of
benefits, this benefit means if he is admitted in the hospital for 10 days, then
you will get this cash
benefit there. Then, there is a case of military hospital
and organ donor transplantation ships, it will
depend on what the
understanding is. Click on the right side, which
is 118. I will put the news list inside.
You can get a claim for that also and in case of fickleness, it is
available for any one case. Then if
someone is admitted in an accident case, then in
such a case, half a spoon of fennel will double. Then
if the typing on room rent is in size 6l
category, then you will get it.  You
can remove your compassion and visit, which means
if someone is admitted in the hospital for five days, then
in such a situation the economy class air
ticket will be cancelled.
If you want to take maternity benefit, then there is a waiting period of 36 months.
Delivery will be done undercover and the
age should be between 18 to 45 years.
Newborn baby comes undercover, this is also a
cancellation. Rest of the claim details,
what did you study, how can you contact them if you
want. I did
not find anything special in the plan and
you do not get its details in a simple way on their website, you have to
contact directly.
It is written right.
Thank you very much that you said this by commenting and
also WhatsApped that I would like to inform you about this.